WE ARE ALL TRYING HERE
Dong-man, it's time to give up.
How long will you pursue something
that's not working?
If you'd gritted your teeth
and gone all in,
you would've made it in ten years.
But you just let 20 years slip by,
just eating and shitting repeatedly.
Instead of holding onto
what won't work out
and getting jealous
of other people's success,
start living more constructively
and productively from now on.
Why the hell does my life
have to please you, sir?
You crazy bastard! What are you doing?
Hey, Dong-man!
Hwang Dong-man!
I'm here!
Hey, Dong-man!
Hwang Dong-man!
Mr. Hwang Dong-man, are you in there?
We're from the Hyoeun Precinct.
Mr. Hwang Dong-man?
Excuse me.
Are you Mr. Hwang Dong-man?
Yes, how can I help you?
Do you live alone?
No.
-Oh, my older brother
-Yes?
works in the countryside,
so he comes and goes.
Then who keeps shouting for you?
-Sorry?
-Huh?
Oh, you see, we received a complaint.
They said someone calls out your name
at all hours of the day,
so they can't get any sleep.
The only Hwang Dong-man
who lives in this area
happens to be you, Mr. Hwang Dong-man.
So who keeps calling for you?
-My brother…
-What about him?
He should call you on his phone instead.
Please tell him to stop shouting for you
because we're getting complaints.
And please open the door quickly
when we call for you.
-Okay.
-All right.
WE SELL GIMBAP
Two rolls of gimbap, please.
Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Have a good day.
Goodbye.
Does Jae-yeong eat braised black beans?
If he says he doesn't, bring it back.
Are you crazy? Why would I beat him up?
I didn't even touch him.
Look.
He was sitting right here,
fidgeting like this,
before he suddenly jumped up
and tried to grab me by the collar.
I don't know if the idiot
tripped over his own feet,
but he reached out like this…
then fell on his face.
Did I touch you at all?
Jeez.
It takes real talent to do that.
I mean, all he had to do
was slide across and…
Is this so hard? Is it?
He's so frustrating.
Then how did he get hurt?
I heard he got a cast.
He probably got drunk and fell on his ass.
I hear the Eight Club is meeting today.
Or should I say the Seven Club?
Anyway, tell Director Park Yeong-su
that I didn't
go for Hwang Dong-man's jugular
to play the hero or something.
I feel crappy about this too.
But since you fine folks
couldn't stand to get your hands dirty,
I did the dirty work for you
because I'm just a lowborn peasant.
You're all so noble, aren't you?
WEATHER MAKER
BY HWANG DONG-MAN
1F: AGIT
2F: KOPARK FILM PRODUCTION
Don't you think Mr. Choi crossed the line?
Who does he think he is,
telling one of us to quit?
We handle our own business.
Who among us will do it?
Think this through, Yeong-su.
Hwang Dong-man
needs to leave this industry.
There's no point staying
because he won't make it.
It's better that he quits
than to go around stirring shit up.
Look at what happened yesterday.
After getting humiliated by Mr. Choi,
you'd think he'd go off the grid
and return with a masterpiece.
Or just grit his teeth
and leave this industry!
Instead, he sent over 100 messages
in our group chat overnight,
complimenting Director Kim's movie,
knowing it's competing
for screens with my movie.
He knows I'm in the group chat.
He's a total lunatic!
It drives him insane
when someone does well.
But he's ecstatic when someone fails.
What an asshole.
When my second movie tanked
right after it was released,
he suddenly sent me a private message,
telling me to keep my chin up
and got me coffee.
Acting all nice and caring.
I felt like shit.
That's the kind of person
Hwang Dong-man is.
There are only two things he does all day.
Dying from jealousy
when someone does well,
and dying from happiness
when he sees someone fail.
Well, I can't say
that I've never felt that way myself.
Of course, everyone feels that way!
But nobody goes as far as Hwang Dong-man!
A normal person would stop and think,
"I'm acting petty. I shouldn't do that."
But that bastard just keeps going!
He's got no self-control!
He won't stop
until we all become failures like him.
It's not just actors
who have to be careful.
We have to be careful too.
Being associated with Hwang Dong-man
is just asking for trouble.
People who are bitter
about their own failures drag others down.
You know what I mean.
He ruins everything wherever he goes.
We're just tossing out a rotten tangerine.
Hwang Dong-man is rotten to the core!
If we leave him be,
the rest of us will rot too!
Damn it, I think I'm already rotting.
But to end
a 20-year relationship like this…
It doesn't sit right with me.
Oh, come on. Stop being so dramatic!
Who cares if it's been 20 years?
People cut family ties these days.
Knowing someone for years isn't important!
They say as you get older,
you have to sort out your relationships.
That's the key to a long and healthy life.
I've been feeling that lately!
Yeong-su.
There's nothing to feel guilty about.
We're not doing anything terrible.
Would you rather we all go down with him?
What about The Eight Club?
Tell me.
Is this the end?
Stop going on about The Eight Club!
We're not a bunch of kids
who formed a club to lean on each other.
Sure, we hung out as a group
when we were younger.
But we don't need to do that anymore
because we can handle ourselves!
Whatever.
I don't care if you keep seeing him
or not, but I'm out.
I'm leaving the group chat,
and I'm done with The Eight Club.
You can become The Seven Club or whatever.
And Hye-jin.
Shut this place down.
I can't stand the sight of that bastard
hanging around here all the time.
Hey, you're at fault too.
You know how much
Dong-man stresses us out,
but you always hold a bottle for him here.
I heard you even call in to check
if he's run out of booze.
You feel sorry for him, but not for me?
He spent the whole night
showering praise on someone else's movie.
Did you even think about
how that made me feel?
Tell me, Lee Jun-hwan.
What about me?
Don't you feel sorry for me?
I do.
I mean, I feel sorry for all of us.
This guy has zero standards.
He'll take anyone who likes him,
even with women.
He has no taste in people whatsoever.
Whatever.
I've said my piece.
I am
leaving The Eight Club.
I'm leaving the group chat too.
Don't invite me anywhere Dong-man will be.
That's it.
I'm done.
The end.
God, that bastard's here again.
That little…
I'm ending this today.
Come on, Gyeong-se.
Not today, all right?
It hasn't been long
since Mr. Choi came down hard on him.
Not today, Gyeong-se.
I'm sorry.
-I'm leaving.
-Where are you…
-That little bastard.
-Gyeong-se!
You're the problem.
Let's go eat!
-Where are you going?
-I have to go home.
What's wrong with your arm?
How did you get hurt?
It's broken.
But it'll heal.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
I want some meat.
Look at the time. We've already eaten.
We have steak, right?
-Cook him one.
-Okay.
What's that?
Is that special effects makeup?
You said you were leaving. Go.
Let's call it a night.
Right, let's go.
Did you punch him?
How can someone's forehead
get so purple?
-I thought you were leaving.
-Want to hear
how this happened?
Yeah.
Don't point your finger at me!
Hey!
He hit it really hard.
There are two kinds of people
in the world.
Those who dedicate themselves
to their own path,
and those who dedicate themselves
to tearing others down.
Right. So?
I said there are two kinds of people
in the world.
Yeah, I heard you.
"Those who dedicate themselves
to their own path,
and those who dedicate themselves
to tearing others down."
The people who dedicate themselves
to tearing others down…
I'm talking to you, you bastard!
-Get out of my way. Hey.
-No, wait.
I'm talking to you!
-Let me go.
-Grab him.
I was talking to you!
I was talking!
-That damn phone.
-Stop it.
-I was talking to you!
-Calm down.
-Give me your phone.
I was talking to you!
Let go of me.
Can I finish what I was saying?
Ready.
Action.
There are two kinds of people
in the world.
Those who dedicate themselves
to their own path,
and those who dedicate themselves
to tearing others down.
Do you know why
the latter will never stop
tearing others down?
Because it's the only way
they can feel superior to everyone else.
That really hits hard, doesn't it?
I was going to crush
that bastard's pride today.
Go again. Get it all out.
Ready.
Action!
There are two kinds of people
in the world.
Those who dedicate themselves
to their own path,
and those who dedicate themselves
to tearing others down.
Nothing cheers you up like meat.
Wine glasses break easily. Take it away.
-Just pour it in this.
-Don't worry.
It's okay if it breaks.
I was feeling like crap,
so I spent all day watching movies
to get a mood-lifting massage.
These people do nothing but make films,
but that's the best they can do?
In my opinion, all Korean film producers
need to take a hard look at themselves.
This is a must
for people in the film industry.
They should watch their own work
and see how they actually feel.
All I get is "bored, bored, bored, bored,
annoyed, annoyed, annoyed,
dull, dull, dull, dull, annoyed, annoyed,
annoyed, annoyed, annoyed."
Why do you think
it's not working out for you?
People crave power.
I hate it when people say "heal the soul"!
I just need something to lift my mood!
What's there to life? Nothing!
But we can't just die either,
so we need enough strength
to get through the day!
That's why people watch movies
and eat good food!
That's why people go on trips,
fall in love, have sex,
get hammered all night long,
and yell at the top of our lungs!
Fuck!
Don't think. Just listen.
Don't think about what to say back
and just listen.
For the next 3 minutes and 27 seconds,
you're not allowed to say a word.
Not a single word until you leave,
so listen up.
You're right.
Life is about
getting mood-lifting massages.
How can I lift my mood?
I work my ass off to make money
and buy clothes, get my nails done,
and do my hair.
But you know what?
You always ruin my mood.
I want the time I spend with friends
to be a chance to show
my easygoing, generous side.
But whenever I see you,
I just end up feeling bitter and drained.
You know that you can't have
a proper conversation with people, right?
Or that you refuse to.
-But I do.
-Shut up.
You just talk nonstop.
That's not true.
Talking to you is impossible,
and you talk nonstop.
And you're all over the place.
And you piss everyone off.
I plan to live to 100,
so I don't want any more stress
because of you.
So as of today,
I'm cutting ties with you.
I created this place to unwind,
so I could eat, drink, and relax
with the people I like.
You're not allowed to come here anymore.
Let's go.
You see,
I'm getting old now.
Listening to someone talk nonstop
scares me more than anything.
Goodbye.
It's been…
Well, I can't say it's been fun.
Just take care.
See you tomorrow.
Don't come back here.
HWANG DONG-MAN NOT ALLOWED
I mean it.
If Hwang Dong-man shows up, kick him out.
HWANG JIN-CHEOL, LEE SUN-OK
The wedding will be
on the 9th of next month.
It's nice to meet you.
He's the older brother,
and he's the younger one.
I've heard a lot about you.
You're a filmmaker, right?
Yes.
You don't need much in a man.
As long as he stays grounded,
has the grit to provide for his family,
and works hard,
that's enough.
Back in the day, you couldn't be buried
in the family cemetery
if you weren't married.
You had to get married, have kids,
and work hard to take care of your family
to earn a place there.
So, how did it go?
-Did you look into it?
-Sorry?
Did you find a celebrity
to sing at Ye-rin's wedding?
You still haven't found one?
I asked you about this ages ago.
You can't do anything.
Look into it right away!
If an elder tells you to do something,
you do it immediately!
Why are you so slow?
He can't book a celebrity for you.
Ask someone else.
He's been in that industry for 20 years.
He doesn't have a close celebrity friend?
No, he doesn't.
-Let's take a photo together.
-I'll take it, ma'am.
Why don't you all stand here?
-You should be in it too.
-It's okay.
-Take it vertically.
-Okay.
-One, two, three.
-Here we go.
You ladies aren't angry, are you?
Here we go.
-One, two, three.
All done.
When there's no welding work,
I harvest napa cabbage in Daegwallyeong.
I work hard and only take
three or four days off a month.
I'm saying Dong-man and I aren't poor
because we're lazy,
just as you didn't become rich
from working hard.
Just admit that you got lucky.
You were lucky to have a man as selfless
as my father as your brother-in-law.
That's the only reason you were able
to take all the Hwang family's fortune.
Just know that I honored
my father's wishes
and refused to get caught up
in a messy inheritance fight,
which is why I live with the pride
of knowing I'm morally superior to you.
At least I came out
with a sense of moral superiority.
But Dong-man just did as I said
because he's got a good heart.
What I'm saying is
you were able to take the family fortune,
thanks to your proud nephew
and your good-hearted one.
Not because you're so diligent
and hardworking!
From now on, don't come
to our grandparents' memorial rites.
The men in the Hwang family
have always been weak.
You spineless bastard.
Why do we have to help
with his damn daughter's wedding?
You really think he asked without knowing
you couldn't pull that off?
He knew but kept pushing
to get what he wanted
because you're a fool!
He knows you'll do anything
if he berates you enough!
You're what they call a pushover, idiot.
You should be swearing at him,
not taking his calls like a dumbass!
Then what?
Should I have said, "I'm incompetent,
so I don't know a single celebrity"?
"I've been in this industry
for 20 years, but I have no influence"?
How can you tell
if the world has ended or not?
It comes down to the weather.
As long as there are clouds in the sky,
wind in the air,
and leaves stirring in the breeze…
As long as weather exists…
the world hasn't ended.
Actor Song's agency called
and asked that we wait a bit longer.
The film they're shooting
has been delayed,
so they haven't had a chance to read it.
Actor Byeon will finish filming this week,
so they'll get back to us by next week.
Is waiting around your job?
You waited last week
and the week before that.
All you've been reporting to me this month
is that you're waiting.
Actor Song doesn't read
other screenplays while filming,
-so as soon as it's over--
-Hey.
Actor Song has a meeting
at Agit today, right?
Yeah. At what time?
Okay, got it.
Don't tell them I'm coming.
Just act like you don't know.
Okay.
Go print out the screenplay.
I said go and print it out!
I wish Mr. Choi
wouldn't treat Eun-a like that
in front of all of us.
It makes me feel like an accomplice,
and I feel bad.
I feel for her,
but she has to handle it on her own.
He doted on her for a while, didn't he?
What happened?
When she started,
she tore into screenplays
with an unbiased perspective.
It was new.
After years of hearing the same clichés
about authenticity and whatnot,
I'm sure Mr. Choi was impressed.
The way Eun-a talks
is raw and instinctive, you know?
And she has those sudden outbursts.
But after a year,
I guess that appeal wore off.
It's like a relationship.
Everything in the first year shines,
with ways of speaking and humor
that are completely new to you.
But after a year, not so much.
That's just how it is.
It's just scary to see someone
fold under like that.
She even stutters now.
It goes to show how fragile people are.
One glance can send them
to heaven or hell.
HANKUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
As I said before,
you're manifesting physical symptoms
from the extreme stress
you're experiencing.
What does the emotion watch say
when you get nosebleeds?
UNKNOWN
Aside from "unknown,"
do any other words appear
when you get nosebleeds?
No.
We need to gather opinions from people
with the same pattern,
and decide what to call this emotion.
But no one else has shown
this type of pattern yet.
Anger, despair, and sadness
make up about 90% of this emotion,
along with a bit of desperation.
What do you think
we should call this emotion?
Can you think back
to how you felt at the time?
Self-destructive.
Like I wanted to self-destruct.
When I was nine.
I was in the second grade.
Even back then,
I'd get nosebleeds in similar situations.
When I felt all alone
and hopeless.
When I was young, I felt hopeless…
and I couldn't breathe.
I still feel the same way,
but now there's an additional feeling.
The feeling of having witnessed
their weakness.
Hey, Hwang! Let's grab some lunch!
DONG-MAN
HWANG DONG-MAN NOT ALLOWED
Welcome.
Hello.
-What can I get you?
-Anything will do.
Who is that?
Dong-man's older brother.
Here you go, sir.
How many degrees is the Earth tilted?
Well?
It's tilted, right?
By 23.5 degrees.
By 23.5 degrees, huh?
The Earth is tilted by 23.5 degrees,
and it produces
9.6 billion tons of food per year.
The global population is 7.7 billion.
Even if each person ate a ton a year,
there'd still be food left over.
All you have to do is sit back
and eat whatever the Earth provides.
Instead, you fill your head with bullshit
about making movies
and go on and on about them.
Such important work, huh?
No one would say anything
if he'd just stop doing crazy things.
He goes around causing trouble
and trying to ruin everything.
Are you bunch so weak that
Hwang Dong-man can ruin you if he tried?
Tell me.
Is Hwang Dong-man really that powerful?
I had no idea.
He's not my son,
but if seeing my 40-year-old brother
get bullied sets me off like this,
I'd go homicidal if he were.
This is the kind of bullying you see
in elementary school, you assholes.
Adults call it cutting ties, not bullying.
Cutting ties as a group
is called bullying, you bastard!
Putting up signs like that
for everyone to see is bullying!
Do you realize
how big a moron your brother is
to make grown-ass adults act like this?
Actually, "moron" sounds too adorable.
Got anything better?
Give me a second.
I'm thinking hard right now.
-Calm down, please.
-Think faster.
An attention-seeking loud-ass
trying to hide how worthless he is
and a complete idiot trying to
convince himself that his shitty situation
-is actually--
-Jin-man!
You piece of shit.
-Hey, get him out of here.
-Let go of me.
Let go of me, punk!
Sorry about that.
-I'm sorry.
-Goddamn it.
What the hell was that?
People like them are making movies?
Hey!
Try being decent human beings first,
you assholes!
No, Jin-man. Just let it go.
-Let go. My bag…
-Please.
I need to go back for my bag!
Let go!
HWANG DONG-MAN AND HIS BROTHER
NOT ALLOWED
Go ahead.
Pick on the brothers!
Dong-man isn't alone in this!
Forget making movies.
Just pack up and come with me, you idiot.
You're 40, not 12.
Why would you get bullied
in your own neighborhood?
I'm not getting bullied!
It was just a little fight!
They admitted they were bullying you!
If you have any pride left,
just leave the industry!
Did you get beaten up?
Of course not!
Then how did you get hurt?
I didn't get hurt!
Then what's with the cast?
This is just…
It's just a joke, okay?
I didn't get hurt!
-Then why the hell do you have a cast on?
-No reason! I just put it on!
You little bastard.
What are you doing?
What are you, a damn kid?
Get your shit together
before I throw you into a mental hospital!
Why would I go to a mental hospital?
What do you even want?
To debut? To be successful?
What is it?
Just tell me, and I'll help you!
Success?
I never said that.
Then what is it?
To not feel anxious.
All I want…
is to not feel anxious.
Find yourself a woman.
You're not brave enough
to grow old and die on your own.
That's just who you are.
You're materialistic
and family-oriented.
So find a woman.
Okay. Give me a minute.
Let's go.
Things are good for at least a month
after a big blow-up.
Oh my gosh. No way.
What is it?
The sign now says "Hwang Dong-man
and his brother not allowed."
No way.
Apparently, his older brother
stopped by and caused a scene.
Those brothers are really something.
Isn't Hye-jin amazing?
She solved the problem with a single sign,
so no one else
had to get their hands dirty.
I know, right?
I can finally relax now.
The thought of not seeing Hwang Dong-man
at Agit makes me so happy.
Why do you all find Director Hwang
so hard to deal with?
You should see for yourself.
To put it simply, he's incompetent.
Being incompetent is fine,
but people who try to cover that up
by talking nonstop
are the absolute worst.
What do you mean by incompetent?
You're a chef, but you can't cook.
You're a teacher, but you can't teach.
Should I continue?
You're human, but you're not humane.
Isn't that peak incompetence?
Seriously?
Are you saying Hwang Dong-man is humane?
And you're saying that we aren't.
So being incompetent makes you humane,
but being competent doesn't?
She said Hwang Dong-man is humane.
I've never heard the word "humane"
sound so damn stupid.
I'd rather be inhumane, then.
Oh, my chest.
Here's to the share hitting 200,000!
-Cheers!
Just a little while ago,
I was fired up to get revenge on Mr. Choi.
-Can we get another bottle of soju?
-One second, please.
I lose my willpower when I'm full.
I have to stay hungry
to be as quick as a wild dog.
-Here's your steamed eggs.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-This looks so good.
Steamed eggs.
JEONG KOREAN BBQ
What happened to your arm?
I got a call from Mr. Choi.
I sent Eun-a my screenplay, you see.
I went there full of hope, but…
I've never heard anything
so hurtful in my life.
My heart started pounding like crazy.
Even more than "unemployed."
And this watch kept vibrating.
What did it say?
"Deeply humiliated"?
HUNGRY
It was scarier than deep humiliation.
It felt like a UFC heavyweight champion
had kicked my ass in the third round.
It hurt so much
that I thought I'd broken some bones.
I felt like I had to
wrap myself up to cope,
so I woke up crying
in the middle of the night
and wrapped myself as tightly as I could.
Only then did it feel like
it didn't hurt as much.
But nope.
I'm not fully healed yet.
It'll take some time to heal.
You know how bones get stronger
after being in a cast?
Just wait.
My confidence, pride,
mental strength, and willpower
will come back way stronger.
They'll never break again.
Hey.
Why are you looking at me so lovingly?
Have you fallen for me?
Jeez, seriously.
I mean,
I wouldn't be surprised if you did.
I don't have any hard feelings
toward Eun-a.
Mr. Choi caught her reading it
because I'd asked her to take a look.
If Eun-a were still in her prime
and had ripped into you,
you wouldn't even be alive.
It amazed me how she'd
tear a screenplay apart without malice.
I once saw Yeong-su look so blank
after Eun-a tore into him,
like his face had disappeared.
He was completely dazed
that his features just vanished.
She ripped into me once too,
but that harsh feedback moved me to tears.
-Come on.
-It was sharp and to the point.
I wanted to gather up
what was left of my brain
-Yeah?
-and beg her, "Tear it apart!"
"Tear it apart!"
I wanted to ask her to go at me again.
You know those stubborn directors
who refuse to make revisions?
Mr. Choi sent Eun-a to the front lines
to tear them apart in his place.
But later, all those directors lined up
wanting to get torn to shreds by her.
When she entered the room,
everyone's eyes lit up.
It made me think,
"So this is what it means to truly shine."
-Come on.
-I'm serious!
Whenever she showed up,
the room would light up,
like someone had flipped a switch.
That's how sharp she used to be.
I like the current Eun-a
better than the sharp Eun-a.
Back then,
she was too…
too intense.
It was uncomfortable.
So why'd she change all of a sudden?
Like she's sick or something.
I don't know.
I don't think she gets along
with anyone at work either.
Why not?
I mean, all the directors
skip Mr. Choi and Hyo-jin.
-If you look at the back…
-They just send
their screenplays
straight to Eun-a for review.
I guess that upsets them.
-How about one more drink?
-What?
-Just one more.
-Forget it. I'm tired.
Go home already.
How do people gain power?
Like a hyena searching for prey
at the foot of a mountain,
I went searching for power.
But I failed, so I'm heading home
right now.
After eating a ton of meat, that is.
Do you happen to know
where they sell power?
I'd like to buy some.
Maybe if you love someone…
What if the protagonist…
was driven by his love for his niece
or nephew who wants to see the weather?
Or maybe
for his beloved older brother?
Then his heart would race,
because he'd do anything
to make it happen.
I realized something
as I read your screenplay.
"Oh…
This director has nothing…
that he loves."
I'm home.
Come on in.
Did he eat it all and not waste anything?
Yes.
Being in love
made everything easy.
But when it ended,
I realized that things I'd forgotten,
and thought were gone,
was still there.
It never left.
This crippling lethargy.
Relax your eyes.
Your eyes.
He's a nobody.
How dare he act like
we're in the same league?
He is in the same league.
You made some movies, and Dong-man didn't.
That's the only difference.
Who's to say he'll never make a movie?
He won't. Ever.
-What if I help him debut?
-Are you crazy?
Why don't you try being a little nicer,
Director Park Gyeong-se?
If you hadn't debuted yet,
would you have acted any differently?
You think you'd have accepted your failure
and lived quietly?
Don't kid yourself.
You would've lost your shit
even worse than Hwang Dong-man.
I knew you would, so I did everything
I could to make sure you debuted.
So I'd never have to
see you hit rock bottom.
How could you say something so harsh?
I'm not done yet!
If you want to be different from him,
then prove that you're different.
You're pitching a fit
because you're just the same.
If he did that to Director Bong Joon-ho,
would he have had a meltdown like you?
No, he'd laugh it off.
If you're truly
on a whole different level,
you have to prove it yourself,
instead of whining and bitching
about how different you two are.
Hey, Dong-man!
Hwang Dong-man!
Hey, you bastard! I'm trying to sleep!
I'm here!
Hey, Dong-man!
Hwang Dong-man!
When I was young, I felt hopeless…
and I couldn't breathe.
I still feel the same way,
but now there's an additional feeling.
The feeling of having witnessed
their weakness.
And that…
makes me feel like I could fight them.
Mr. Choi Dong-hyeon, are you in there?
DIRECTOR'S ROOM 4
Hwang Dong-man is here.
It's okay. Let him stay.
You divide people into classes,
keeping the successful, shiny ones close,
while treating losers like me
as if we've got some contagious disease
and trying to shove us aside.
Go ahead and try building a shiny world
with just the shiny people.
It won't shine at all.
By the way, I'm freaking good at
talking behind people's backs.
I told you to stop saying
words like "freaking," you bastard.
Stop calling me "bastard"!
And don't interrupt me.
I'm normally freaking talkative,
but I held my tongue and listened to you.
So now it's your turn to listen.
That's showing respect in a conversation!
Okay.
Go ahead, I'll listen.
Damn it, I forgot.
Let me start over.
Listen carefully.
Ready.
Action.
Do you know why so many murders occur?
Disrespect. Complete disrespect.
The only reason you didn't die that day
is because I'm a saint.
I'm freaking good at
talking behind people's backs.
But do you know why
I never do it to someone's face?
Because it's the polite thing to do.
Then I saw you and realized
that people in this industry think
saying things to someone's face
gives them power.
They think calling a loser a loser
is some brilliant insight
they came up with themselves.
They think being a rude-ass
gives them power.
If that's the case,
I'll say it to your face too.
I'm done talking behind people's backs.
I'll just say it in front of everybody.
All of you.
I'll say it to your faces.
Look forward to it.
Here's what I came to tell
Choi Dong-hyeon to his face.
Don't act like you're the adult here.
Nobody here asked you to.
And stop sending your innocent juniors
to the front lines
to take shots at directors
who don't listen to you.
What are they, cannon fodder?
And just you wait.
I'm about to become something incredible.
I'm going to become incredibly
and even more, more, more, more worthless,
and even more, more, more, more useless.
And I'm going to piss you all off
more and more and more and more!
Brace yourselves.
You'll end up waving a white flag.
And finally!
I'm going to pull up the shiny truth…
from the very depths of my worthlessness.
Look forward to my shiny story.
Stop me if you can.
I dare you to.
Hang on.
It's my turn to talk.
No thanks, I'm busy.
Has he been day drinking or what?
Did you just laugh?
Look at you, all cheerful and smiling.
That's a first.
Cut.
I just fell in love with myself.
I love this guy.
I think I can even have sex with myself.
What should I do?
This guy is so cool.
Every day is just spectacular
thanks to Hwang Dong-man…
I can't talk. My lungs hurt too much.
What's wrong?
I started choking when I was talking shit
about Hwang Dong-man yesterday.
I thought I was going to die
and almost called 911.
When I get nosebleeds from stress…
It's my body telling me
I'm killing myself.
It shows
how powerful the mind is.
I understand that much.
But…
is it possible to go from hurting myself…
to hurting someone else?
She said Hwang Dong-man is humane.
I've never heard the word "humane"
sound so damn stupid.
I'd rather be inhumane, then.
Oh, my chest.
…and productively from now on.
You crazy bastard! What are you doing?
That day.
I've been replaying that day in my head,
down to every tenth of a second.
And I'm positive Hwang Dong-man
never even brushed against me.
But…
it was strange.
You know what?
He must be possessed.
They're side dishes.
My grandmother made them.
You can have them.
We're in sync.
Thank you.
You're…
more beautiful than the weather.
WE ARE ALL TRYING HERE
Eun-a!
When I'm with someone who likes me,
I become really gentle.
You seem like someone
with a thousand doors wide open.
I'll see for myself
what Hwang Dong-man is like.
Gyeong-se can never see this.
Hwang Dong-man!
You're just a nobody.
Is it Hwang Dong-man this time?
I wish you'd just die.
Whenever I come across
a similar situation,
I'm right back at that moment,
paralyzed with fear.
Who do you think it was?
Who do you think was the first person
to cross you off?
Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim